Guide to the Hovander Family and Park Papers 1844-1996
Western Washington University, Center for Pacific Northwest Studies
- Hovander Park Interpretive Materials, circa 1940s-1996; Series II
  - Oral Histories, 1994-1996; Sub-series 2
    - Amanda, Charles & Harlin Hovander (With cassette tape), 1994-1995 (Box-folder 27/12)
    - Chet Speziale (with cassette tape and photograph), 1994 (Box-folder 27/13)
    - Denis Demeyer, 1996 (Box-folder 27/14)
    - Jamie Ashton, Jim Edwards, Bob Penny-Brown, Nelda Sigurdson, Dave Simonson, and Don Wright, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 27/15)
    - John and Verna Friend, A. Winisky (With cassette tape and photographs), 1994 (Box-folder 27/16)
    - Otis Hovander (Cassette tape as well as 3 ¼” Mylar reel tape, no transcripts), Undated (Box-folder 27/17)
    - Steve Hovander, 1994 (Box-folder 27/18)